[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What day marks the start of Easter fasting in Eastern Christianity?", "correct_answer": "Clean Monday", "incorrect_answers": ["Good Friday", "Palm Sunday", "Lazarus Saturday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Extraterrestrial life may be closer than we think. Which of these natural satellites of Saturn is believed to have suitable conditions for existence of life?", "correct_answer": "Titan", "incorrect_answers": ["Phoebe", "Dione", "Atlas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the main ingredients of the traditional English dish Bubble and Squeak?", "correct_answer": "Potato and cabbage", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish and ships", "Sausage and cabbage", "Bacon and eggs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Octopuses can not be kept as pets.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many US states were there in 1800?", "correct_answer": "16", "incorrect_answers": ["22", "3", "30"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Godzilla vs. Hedorah (1971), a socially conscious entry in the series, what ecological problem was addressed by the storyline?", "correct_answer": "Pollution", "incorrect_answers": ["Nuclear Power Accidents", "Strip Mining", "Deforestation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Lanthanum?", "correct_answer": "La", "incorrect_answers": ["Ln", "L", "Lt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is regarded as the first professional (American style) football player?", "correct_answer": "William Heffelfinger", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Grange", "Jay Berwanger", "Jim Thorpe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many Orcs participate in the battle of Helms Deep in the movie Lord of the Rings?", "correct_answer": "10,000", "incorrect_answers": ["500,000", "50,000", "100,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All turtles withdraw their head into their shell by contracting their neck to the side.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A common complaint among pregnant women are swollen legs.  Feet actually swell because of this.", "correct_answer": "Water retention", "incorrect_answers": ["Tight Shoes", "Constipation", "Indigestion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The optimal position for a knight is the edge of the chess board.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]